University of Connecticut 1989.0024
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series IX: Publications, 1944-1983
  - Subseries C: Guides, 1950-1983
    - Library Guides (Box 44)
      - Public Opinion Surveys
      - Public School Finance
      - Public Speaking
      - Puerto Rico
      - Reference Collection Booklet
      - Reference Sources
      - Russia and Eastern Europe
      - Scavenger Hunt
      - Science Fiction
      - Serials List
      - Shakespeare
      - Short Stories
      - Sociology
      - Social Statistics
      - Soviet Foreign Policy
      - State Publications
      - Statistics
      - STN International
      - Style Manuals
      - Tax forms
      - Transportation Engineering
      - Treaties
      - UConn Buildings
      - United Nations
      - USSR
      - Video Library
      - Women and Politics
      - Womens Studies
      - Anthropology
      - Art and Architecture
      - Art Criticism
      - Bibliographic Citation
      - Biographies
      - Biotechnology
      - Black Studies
      - Book Reviews
      - British Parliamentary Papers
      - Business Records
      - Census
      - Chemical Abstracts
      - Chemical Prices
      - Chemistry
      - Children's Literature
      - Chinese
      - Civil Engineering
      - Computer Science
      - Criminology
      - Current Events
      - Dancing
      - Design Methodology
      - Dramatic Arts
      - Drug Information
      - Early American Newspapers
      - Education, Higher
      - Eighteenth Century Short Title Catalogue
      - Email
      - Encyclopedia
      - Engineering
      - European History
      - Exporting
      - Ferderal Government Publications (Box 70)
      - Federal Regulations
      - Film Reviews
      - Fish and Wildlife Management
      - Folklore and Myth
      - Foreign and International Economic Statistics
      - Foreign Broadcasr Information Services
      - Foreign Exchange Rates
      - Foreign Relations
      - French Language and Literature
      - Genealogy
      - Genetics
      - Geology
      - German Studies
      - Government Publications
      - Graduate Programs
      - Grants, Scholarships, and Fellowships
      - Great Britain
      - Group Studies
      - Hartford
      - History
      - Human Development and Family Relations
      - Ichthyology
      - Industry Statistics
      - Investment Information
      - Italian Language and Literature
      - Labor Relations
      - Landscape Architecture Research
      - Latin America
      - Latino/a Studies
      - Legal Reference Materials
      - Legislative History: CT
      - Legislative History: US
      - Library Adventure
      - Library Fact Sheet
      - Library Rally
  - Subseries D: Readings, 1972-1977
    General note
    [Note: See also Series XIII.]
    - 5 Writers, 1974 December 5 (Box 19)
    - Creeley, Robert: poet, 1974 March 28
    - Daigon, Ruth: poet, 1974 September 12
    - Dawson, Fielding, 1974 March 28
    - Dorbin, Sandy: poet, 1974 June 11
    - Duncan, Robert: Reading at Wallace Stevens Memorial Program, 1972 April 25
    - Glover, Albert: poet, 1973 October 11
    - Goodell, Larry: poet, 1973 April 4
    - Hall, Joan Joffee: poet, 1977 March 29
    - Kelly, Robert: poet, 1974 October 7
    - Kinsella, Thomas: poet, 1975 April 22
    - Koller, James: poet, 1974 January 24
    - McKain, David: poet, 1974 September 26
    - Oppenheimer, Joel: poet, 1975 March 26
    - Raworth, Tom: poet, 1975 January 30
    - Rumaker, Michael: poet, 1976 April 1
    - Stein, Charles: poet, 1973 November 29
    - Tate, James: poet, 1974 April 23
    - Waldman, Anne: poet, 1975 March 4
    - Williams, Jonathan: poet, 1974 December 11
    - Wright, Charles: poet, 1975 November 18
    - Young, Virginia Brady: poet, 1975 November 30
  - Subseries E: Other, 1959-1973
    - Hollo, Anslem: Poet, Postmodern Writing Series, 1973
    - Services for the Handicapped, undated
    - Publications, 1992-1996 (Box 65)
- Series X: Staff Materials, circa 1970
  - AAUP and FUT Newsletters, undated (Box 20)
  - Articles, undated
  - Ballots, Notices, Questionnaires to Library Staff, undated
  - Faculty Status, undated
  - Legal Miscellany, Librarians Included in Bargaining Unit, undated
  - News Articles, undated
  - Staff transfers, undated, 1979-2000 (Box 91)
    Scope and Content Note
    [Subjects include: administrative records, publications, reports, studies, minutes.]
- Series XI: Construction of Homer Babbidge Library, 1969-1977
  - 1969 (Box 21)
  - 1970-1972
  - 1973-1974
  - 1974-1975
  - 1975-1976
  - 1976-1977
  - ARL, undated
  - Building Elements, undated
  - Capital Project Fund Request, undated
  - Change Orders, undated
  - Correspondence, undated
    - Architect, undated
    - Architect, undated
    - Physical Plant, undated
    - Other, undated
  - Design Criteria, undated
  - Design Criteria, 1970 April 6
  - Design Criteria, Basic Stage, 1970 August 15
  - Enrollment, undated
  - Functions of the New Research Library, undated
  - Funds for Library Acquisitions, undated
  - Handicapped, undated
  - Interiors Consultant, undated
  - Library Trends, undated
  - Manual of Information and Instructions, Preparation and Submission of Proposals, undated
  - New Library - Numbers, undated
  - Notes, undated
  - Outline Specifications, undated
  - Project Manual, Architectural, 1971 July 1 (Box 22)
  - Project Manual, Mechanical, 1971 July 1
  - Purchasing, undated
  - Quality in Architecture, undated
  - Report for Trustees, undated
  - Research Library - Program, undated
  - Space Needs, undated
  - Status Report, undated
  - Transmittals from Architect, undated
  - University Capital Building Program, undated
  - Vertical Circulation, undated
  - Wilbur Cross Library Addition - Program, undated
- Series XII: Library Development Office, undated, 1988-1999
  These materials concern the planning and funding of the "Dodd Year" and are restricted to Library Development staff only. Information on the actual events and recordings of the presentations are available at the Dodd Research Center.
- Series XIII: Committee (Team) Records, 1974-2005
  - Subseries A: Advisory Council on the Evaluation and Promotion of Professional Librarians (ACEP), 1974-2005
    - ACEP, 1974-2005
  - Subseries B: Poetry Committee, 1974-1975
    - Adam, Helen-"Turn Again to Me", undated (Box 24)
    - Dorfman, Elsa, undated
    - Kinsella, Thomas-"Blessed William Skullbullet", "A figure struck and lodged up," and "You will note firstly", undated
    - McKain, David, undated
    - Waldman, Anne-"Lady tactics", undated
  - Subseries C: User Team, 1997-2006
    - Final report, 1997 (Box 25)
    - Completed survey forms, 1997
    - Avery Point Library Item 9_7 by Item 10 to Item 12, 1997
    - Stamford-Jeremy Richard Library Item 9_9 by Item 10 to Item 12, 1997
    - Crosstabulations, 1997
    - #2-Campus by questions 2-8, 1997
    - #3-Campus by Collections and services--#1 by #10-12,#3-Campus by Collections and services--#1 by #10-12, 1997
    - #3-Campus by Collections and services--Item 13 by Item 14_1, 1997
    - #4-Anova Item 1 vs. I13, 1997
    - #4-Campus by questions 13-19, 1997
    - #5-Department by Collections and services
      - Item 11_41 to Item 11_6f, 1997
      - Item 11_7a to Item 11_9f, 1997
      - Item 11_10a to Item 12_1f, 1997
      - Item 12_2a to Item 12_5c, 1997
      - Item 12_5c to Item 12_7f, 1997
      - Item 12_7f to Item 12_10f, 1997
      - Item 12_10a to Item 12_11f, 1997
    - #5a-Department by question 10, 1997
    - #5b-Department by 11_1a to 11_3f, 1997 (Box 26)
    - #6-Department by
      - Item 13 to Item 14_12, 1997
      - Item 14_12 by item 15_13, 1997
      - Item 16_1 to Item 17_12, 1997
      - Item 18_1 to Item 19_6, 1997
    - #11-Lower Division students by current use of Libraries (#10), 1997
    - #12-Lower Division students by questions 13-19, 1997
    - #12-Graduate students by questions 13-19, 1997
    - #12-No students by questions 13-19, 1997
    - #13-Purpose by satisfaction with services
      - Item 11_2f by Item 14_12, 1997
      - Item 11_4f by Item 14_12, 1997
      - Item 11_6f by Item 14_12, 1997
      - Item 11_8f by Item 14_12, 1997
      - Item 11_10f by Item 14_12, 1997
      - Item 11_12f by Item 14_12, 1997
    - Frequencies for the 6 non UConn Library Users, 1997
    - Frequencies and percents for questions 1-20, 1997
    - For School by
      - Item 10_1, 1997
      - Item 11, 1997
      - Item 12_1a, 1997
      - Item 13, 1997
      - Item 14, 1997
      - Item 15, 1997
      - Item 16, 1997
      - Item 17, 1997
      - Item 18_1, 1997
      - Item 19_1, 1997
    - Journals, Unbound-Current, 1997 (Box 27)
    - Newspaper-Open Reading Area, 1997
    - Undergraduate Survey
      - Identified, 1997
      - Regionals-Avery Point, 1997
      - Regionals-Hartford, 1997
      - Regionals-Stamford, 1997
      - Regionals-Torrington, 1997
      - Regionals-Waterbury, 1997
      - Storrs, 1997
    - 2011-0014 accession, 1997-2006 (Box 87)
      - Undergraduate Student Survey, 1997-1998
      - Graduate Student Survey, 1998-1999
      - Summary report survey, 2006 Spring
      - Final Report survey, 2006 Spring
      - Project SAILS (Standardized Assessment of Information Literacy Skills), 2005
      - Preliminary results Undergraduate survey, 1998
  - Subseries D: Exhibit Committee, 2003-2009
    - Correspondence, Minutes, Publications, Photographs, 2003-2009 (Box 90, Box 89)
- Series XIV: Audiovisual materials, 1996-2001
  - Video cassettes
    - Library forum [2001]. Recorded at the Dodd Research Center of the University of Connecticut. Library director Brinley Franklin speaks on the Library's 2001-2002 goals, and progress on past goals including the hiring of new staff and the reorganization of the Collection Services department. Tom Wilsted and Ken Neubeck speak on the "Human Rights Semester" program, 2001 September 18 (Cassette Video)
    - Humor in the workplace. Barreca, Regina. University of Connecticut. Libraries. Library Forum Team. University of Connecticut. Libraries. Development Office, [2001] (Cassette Video)
    - Holocaust wall hangings / produced by Judith Weinshall Liberman and Bob Lewis; directed by Bob Lewis. Newton, MA: Judith Liberman. Narrated by Leonard Zola. Artwork photographed at the DeCordova Museum in Lincoln, Mass. The artist talks about creating her exhibition of Holocaust wall hangings. Individual pieces are shown and explained, circa 1996 (Cassette Video)
  - Audio cassettes
    - Stars on the Home Front (Cassette AC)
    - A Moving Experience (Cassette AC)
    - Care and Handling (Cassette AC)
    - Husky Welcome (Cassette AC)
    - Library of Congress Classification System (Cassette AC)
    - Dewey Decimal System (Cassette AC)
  - Slide Shows (Box 77)
    - Husky "Welcome"
    - Preservation
    - Library of Congress Classification System
    - Dewey Decimal System
    - A Moving Experience
    - Stars on the Home Front
- Series XV: Music and Dramatic Arts Library Renovation, 1991-2000
  - Liaison Profiles (Box 88)
  - Microfilm cabinets
  - Audio carrels--Data and power maps
  - Compact stacks
  - Compact stacks-- SpaceSaver
  - Computer equipment
  - Copier
  - Correspondence
  - Drawings
  - Correspondence--Haworth modules
  - Joe's office
  - Listening system
  - Move
  - Move lists
  - Periodical racks
  - Project description and original equipment list
  - Security issues
  - Shelving--Estey, list rack
  - Telecommunications
  - Video equipment
  - SpaceSaver
  - AV
  - Maps
  - Circulation counter
  - Carpet
  - Cookson window
  - New building
  - Move
  - Move collections plans
  - AV
  - CTech problem
  - AV--Crimson Tech
  - Furniture
  - AV issues
  - AV proposal
  - Furniture
  - Budgets
  - Equipment memoranda and lists
  - Layouts
  - Furniture
  - Progress meetings
  - Shelving (Box 91)
  - Photographs